https://www.militarypresentations.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Historical
Armour (Miniature)
Helmets (1/2 Scale) Collectables
New Products ...
All Products ...
Your cart is empty.
Historical
Armour (Miniature)
Helmets (1/2 Scale) Collectables
New Products ...
All Products ...
New Products -   [more]
Discount Coupons
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Customer Internet Privacy StatementAt Metalcraft By Blair, we greatly appreciate your business and protecting your privacy is of utmost importance to us. We want you, the consumer, to have a complete understanding of what information we gather from you and what we do with this information. This policy effects the entire Metalcraft By Blair website and is current as of December 28, 2003.When coming to our website, we collect some basic information such as your IP address and the internet browser you are using. Our site retrives this data with session cookies, which are deleted after the user leaves the Metalcraft By Blair website. We do not place any tracking cookies on your computer. When doing business with Metalcraft By Blair, we collect information from you such as your address, email address, and phone number in order to process and ship your order.The information we collect from the session cookies is used for site management purposes. We also use this data to generate aggregate, broad statistics on what product lines are most popular. Your personal information gathered by doing business with us is used only for completing customer transactions and tracking sales. We will not disclose this information to any marketing firm or other third-party entity, and we will not use this information for future marketing purposes. Any data collected is strictly confidential. All of this information is stored on our secure server with 128-bit SSL(Secure Socket Layer) encryption.If you have any further questions about our privacy policy, you can email us at metalcraftbyblair@aol.com or call us at 304-277-4161. This policy is subject to change and it is the consumer's responsiblity to check this policy frequently for any changes.
We acceptContact InformationSite InformationDeliveries & Returns
Address: Military Presentations
170 N. 17th St.
Wheeling, WV 26003
Tel: 304-277-4161HomeFeatured ProductsSpecialsNew ProductsAll Products ...
Copyright © 2020 Military Presentations. Hosting and Support by Wheaton Website Services.
